Guide to the "How I Write" Podcast, Records SC1291
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
"How I Write" Podcast, Records
2002-2014
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Obenzinger, Hilton
SC1291
8 Linear Feet
Biographical / Historical
Sponsored by the Hume Center for Writing and Speaking, “How I Write” is a podcast hosted by Hilton Obenzinger. Each quarter Obenzinger invites authors across disciplines to share about their writing styles and habits. Past guests have included Stanford President John Hennessey, English professor and director of American Studies Shelley Fisher Fishkin and political science professor Terry Karl. Other speakers have included scientists such as Richard Zare and computer scientist Eric Roberts. For more about this program, visit: https://undergrad.stanford.edu/tutoring-support/hume-center/about-hume-center/annual-events/how-i-write-series
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Hilton Obenzinger, 2016.
Authors; Authorship; Authors -- Interviews; Obenzinger, Hilton; Obenzinger, Hilton
- Interview Files
  - David Rasch, 2003 Nov 7 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Rob Reich, 2009 Apr 9 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - John Richford, 2002 Apr 24 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Eric Roberts, 2003 Mar (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Lou Roberts, 2002 Jan 30 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Robinson/Ngai (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Robinson/Ngai, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Terry Root, 2008 Feb 4 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Richard Rorty, 2004 Nov 9 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Renato Rosalto, 2002 Apr 17 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Robert Sapolsky, 2003 Apr 9 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Rawm Saldivan, 2007 Nov 14 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Scott Saul (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Debra Satz, 2004 Mar 3 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Rebecca Slayton, 2008 Jan 21 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Rebecca Solvit, 2010 Apr 29 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Peter Stansky (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Claude Steele (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Leonard Susskind, 2007 May 2 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Phil Taubman, 2009 Nov 11 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Scan Teuton (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Fred Turen, 2007 Feb 7 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Abraham Verghese, 2011 May 4 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Victor Wooten, 2010 May (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Richard Zare, 2008 Oct 14 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Zipperstein, 2005 Apr 21 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Irv Yalom, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Marilyn Yalom, 2014 Feb 19 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Alex Woloch, 2002 Mar 6 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Richard Zare (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - How I Write (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - How I Write (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - David Abevrethy (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Akalitis + levaett, 2007 Nov 1 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Molly Antopol/ Scott Hutchins (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Don Barr (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Joel Beinin (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Joel Beinin Tigerfish (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Eavan Boland, 2004 Oct 13 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - David Brody (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - John Bravman (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Jerry Castle (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Terry Colte notes (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Harriet Chessman (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Stanford daily (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Diane Di Prima (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Diane Di Prima (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - David Dunaway, 2009 Apr 20 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Paulla Ebon, 2006 Oct 10 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Penny Echert (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Harry Elam, 2004 Apr 28 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Nancy Etchemendy, 2008 Nov 15 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Shelley Fisher Fishkin, 2005 May 12 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Richard T. Ford, 2009 Apr 16 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Amy Freed, 2006 Oct 25 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Estelle Freedman, 2003 Oct 29 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - George Fredrickson, 2003 May 8 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - A. Gelpi (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - grad students, 2002 Dec 4 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Bill Guttentag, 2012 Feb 9 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Tom Hare, 2012 May 14 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - John Hennessy, 2004 Apr 13 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - David Henry Hwang, 2007 Feb 13 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - David Henry Hwang (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Troy Jollimore, 2007 Apr 25 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Addam Johnson, 2012 Oct 23 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Clarence Jones (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Jones, lecturer (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Terry Karl (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - David Kennedy (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Donald Kennedy (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Susan Krieger, 2012 Apr 25 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Gwyneth Lewis, 2010 Mar 8 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Andrea Lunsford, 2003 Jan 16 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Scotty McLennan (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Diane Middlebrook (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Malki, Roberts, Shloss, 2008 Apr 17 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Hazel Markus, 2005 Nov 8 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Abbas Milani, 2011 Oct 26 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Valorie Minen, 2008 Apr 30 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Ian Morris (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Paula Moya, 2004 Feb 3 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Anne Firth Murray, 2006 Jan 25 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Hilton O., 2007 Oct 23 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - the Stanford Daily newspaper, 2007 Oct 24 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - PWR faculty, 2005 Jan 27 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Nancy Packer (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Marjorie Perloff (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Arnold Rampersad, 2007 May 21 (Box 2, Folder 57)
- Audiovisual Materials
  - David Abernethy, 2002 Feb 13; 3_001; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Penelope Eckert, 2003 May 22; 3_002; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Harry Elam, 2004 Apr 28; 3_003; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Paula Moya, 2004 Feb 3; 3_004; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - David Abernethy, 2002 Feb 13; 3_005; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Eric Roberts, 2002 Nov 21; 3_006; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Paula Moya, 2004 Feb 3; 3_007; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Anne Firth Murray, 2006 Jan 25; 3_008; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Marjarie Perloff, undated; 3_009; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Terry Karl, 2004 Oct 26; 3_010; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - George Fredrickson, 2003 May 8; 3_011; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Eric Roberts, 2002 Nov 21; 3_012; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - John Hennessy, 2004 Apr 13; 3_013; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - David Kennedy, undated; 3_014; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Jones lectures, 2006 Feb 15; 3_015; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Jones lectures, 2006 Feb 15; 4_001; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Robert Sapolsky, 2003 Apr 9; 4_002; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Robert Sapolsky, 2003 Apr 9; 4_003; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Eavan Boland, 2004 Oct 13; 4_004; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Paul Robinson, Sianne Ngai, 2002 Jun 5; 4_005; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Diane Middlebrook (fast forward 5 minutes to get to start of interview), 2002 Oct 15; 4_006; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Diane Middlebrook, 2002 Oct 15; 4_007; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Lou Roberts, 2002 Jan 30; 4_008; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - John Bravman, 2003 Jan 28; 4_009; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Donald Barr, 2003 Nov 6; 4_010; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Estelle Freedman, 2003 Oct 29; 4_011; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Graduate student writing dissertations, 2002 Dec 4; 4_012; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Scotty McLennan, 2003 Feb 26; 4_013; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Steve Zipperstein, 2005 Apr 20; 4_014; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - David Brady, 2005 Jan 13; 4_015; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Donald Kennedy, 2005 Feb 23; 4_016; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Renato Rosalto, 2002 Apr 17; 4_017; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Andrea Lunsford, 2003 Jan 16; 4_018; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - PWR faculty roundtable, 2005 Jan 27; 4_019; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Alex Woloch, 2002 Mar 6; 4_020; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Alex Woloch, 2002 Mar 6; 4_021; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Lou Roberts, 2002 Jan 30; 4_022; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - John Rickford, 2002 Apr; 4_023; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Claude Steele, 2004 Feb 19; 4_024; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Scotty McLennan, 2003 Feb 26; 4_025; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - John Rickford, 2002 Apr 24; 4_026; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Debra Satz, 2004 Mar 3; 4_027; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Richard Rorty, 2004 Nov 9; 4_028; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Shelley Fisher Fishkin, 2005 May 12; 4_029; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - David Rasch, 2003 Nov 17; 4_030; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Fred Turner, 2007 Feb 7; 5_001; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - John Rickford (audio), 2002 Apr 24; 5_002; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Fred Turner, 2007 Feb 7; 5_003; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Amy Freid audio, 2006 Oct 25; 5_004; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Richard Ford, undated; 5_005; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Leonard Susskind, 2007 May 2; 5_006; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Leonard Susskind, 2007 May 2; 5_007; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Leonard Susskind, 2007 May 2; 5_008; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Leonard Susskind, 2007 May 2; 5_009; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Leonard Susskind, 2007 May 2; 5_010; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Leonard Susskind, 2007 May 2; 5_011; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Leonard Susskind, 2007 May 2; 5_012; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Leonard Susskind, 2007 May 2; 5_013; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Leonard Susskind, 2007 May 2; 5_014; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - unlabeled, undated; 5_015; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - unlabeled, undated; 5_016; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Rebecca Solnit, undated; 5_017; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Rebecca Solnit, undated; 5_018; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Troy Jollimore, 2007 Apr 25; 5_019; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Tory Jollimore, 2007 Apr 25; 5_020; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Troy Jollimore, 2007 Apr 25; 5_021; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Troy Jollimore, 2007 Apr 25; 5_022; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Troy Jollimore, 2007 Apr 25; 5_023; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Troy Jollimore, 2007 Apr 25; 5_024; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Renato Rosalto, 2002 Apr 17; 5_025; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Fred Turner, 2007 Feb 7; 5_026; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Fred Turner, 2007 Feb 7; 5_027; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Fred Turner, 2007 Feb 7; 5_028; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Fred Turner, 2007 Feb 7; 5_029; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Richard Zare, 2008 Oct 14; 5_030; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Richard Zare, 2008 Oct 14; 5_031; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Richard Zare, 2008 Oct 14; 5_032; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Fred Turner audio, 2007 Feb 7; 5_033; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Richard Zare, 2008 Oct 14; 5_034; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Richard Zare, 2008 Oct 14; 5_035; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Richard Zare, 2008 Oct 14; 5_036; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Richard Zare, 2008 Oct 14; 5_037; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Steve Zipperstein, 2005 Apr 21; 5_038; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Rebecca Solnit, undated; 5_039; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Hiton Obenzinger, 2007 Oct 23; 5_040; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Hiton Obenzinger, 2007 Oct 23; 5_041; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Hiton Obenzinger, 2007 Oct 23; 5_042; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Hiton Obenzinger, 2007 Oct 23; 5_043; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Hiton Obenzinger, 2007 Oct 23; 5_044; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Renato Rosalto, 2002 Apr 17; 5_045; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Professor Ramon Saldivar, 2007 Nov 14; 5_046; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Hiton Obenzinger, 2007 Oct 23; 5_047; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Hiton Obenzinger, 2007 Oct 23; 5_048; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Hilton Obenzinger, 2007 Oct 23; 5_049; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Hilton Obenzinger, 2007 Oct 23; 5_050; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Hilton Obenzinger, 2007 Oct 23; 5_051; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Hilton Obenzinger, 2007 Oct 23; 5_052; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Hilton Obenzinger, 2007 Oct 23; 5_053; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Alex Woloch, 2002 Mar 6; 5_054; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Dr. Terry Root, 2008 Feb 4; 5_055; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Dr. Terry Root, 2008 Feb 4; 5_056; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Dr. Terry Root, 2008 Feb 4; 5_057; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Dr. Terry Root, 2008 Feb 4; 5_058; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Dr. Terry Root, 2008 Feb 4; 5_059; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Dr. Terry Root, 2008 Feb 4; 5_060; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Dr. Terry Root, 2008 Feb 4; 5_061; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Dr. Terry Root, 2008 Feb 4; 5_062; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Dr. Terry Root, 2008 Feb 4; 5_063; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Dr. Terry Root, 2008 Feb 4; 5_064; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Paul Robinson tape 2 and 1, 2002 May 15; 5_065; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Sianne Ngai, 2002 Jun 5; 5_066; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Robert Sapolsky, 2003 Apr 9; 5_067; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Troy Jollimore, 2007 Apr 25; 5_068; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Scotty Mcllennon (audio), undated; 5_069; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Scotty Mcllenon (audio), undated; 5_070; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Diane Middlebrook (audio), undated; 5_071; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Diane Middlebrook (audio), undated; 5_072; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Liisa Malkki, Richard Roberts Carol Shloss, 2008 Apr 17; 5_073; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Liisa Malkki, Richard Roberts Carol Shloss, 2008 Apr 17; 5_074; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Liisa Malkki, Richard Roberts Carol Shloss, 2008 Apr 17; 5_075; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Liisa Malkki, Richard Roberts Carol Shloss, 2008 Apr 17; 5_076; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Liisa Malkki, Richard Roberts Carol Shloss, 2008 Apr 17; 5_077; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Liisa Malkki, Richard Roberts Carol Shloss, 2008 Apr 17; 5_078; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Liisa Malkki, Richard Roberts Carol Shloss, 2008 Apr 17; 5_079; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Liisa Malkki, Richard Roberts Carol Shloss, 2008 Apr 17; 5_080; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Liisa Malkki, Richard Roberts Carol Shloss, 2008 Apr 17; 5_081; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Liisa Malkki, Richard Roberts Carol Shloss, 2008 Apr 17; 5_082; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Liisa Malkki, Richard Roberts Carol Shloss, 2008 Apr 17; 5_083; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Liisa Malkki, Richard Roberts Carol Shloss, 2008 Apr 17; 5_084; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Liisa Malkki, Richard Roberts Carol Shloss, 2008 Apr 17; 5_085; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Victor L. Wooten, undated; 5_086; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Victor L. Wooten, undated; 5_087; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Victor L. Wooten, undated; 5_088; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Rebecca Solnit, undated; 5_089; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Rebecca Solnit, undated; 5_090; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Hilton Obenzinger, 2007 Oct 23; 5_091; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - David Dunaway, 2009 Apr 20; 5_092; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - David Dunaway, 2009 Apr 20; 5_093; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - James Hohmann, Julie Klein, Daniel Novinson Emma Trotter, 2008 Jan 23; 5_094; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - James Hohmann, Julie Klein, Daniel Novinson Emma Trotter, 2008 Jan 23; 5_095; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - James Hohmann, Julie Klein, Daniel Novinson Emma Trotter, 2008 Jan 23; 5_096; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Prof. Terry Castle, 2009 Feb 11; 5_097; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Prof. Terry Castle, 2009 Feb 11; 5_098; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Nancy Etchemendy, 2008 Nov 15; 5_099; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Nancy Etchemendy, 2008 Nov 15; 5_100; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Nancy Etchemendy, 2008 Nov 15; 5_101; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - James Hohmann, Julie Klein, Daniel Novinson Emma Trotter, 2008 Jan 23; 5_102; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - James Hohmann, Julie Klein, Daniel Novinson Emma Trotter, 2008 Jan 23; 5_103; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - James Hohmann, Julie Klein, Daniel Novinson Emma Trotter, 2008 Jan 23; 5_104; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - James Hohmann, Julie Klein, Daniel Novinson Emma Trotter, 2008 Jan 23; 5_105; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - James Hohmann, Julie Klein, Daniel Novinson Emma Trotter, 2008 Jan 23; 5_106; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - James Hohmann, Julie Klein, Daniel Novinson Emma Trotter, 2008 Jan 23; 5_107; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Shelley Fisher Fishkin, 2005 May 12; 5_108; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Harry Elam, 2004 Apr 28; 5_109; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Penelope Eckert, undated; 5_110; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Paulla ebron, 2006 Oct 10; 5_111; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Prof. Terry Castle, 2009 Feb 11; 5_112; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Prof. Terry Castle, 2009 Feb 11; 5_113; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Prof. Terry Castle, 2009 Feb 11; 5_114; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - unlabeled, undated; 5_115; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Anne Firth Murray, undated; 5_116; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Anne Firth Murray, 2006 Jan 25; 5_117; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Anne Firth Murray, 2006 Jan 25; 5_118; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Anne Firth Murray, 2006 Jan 25; 5_119; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Anne Firth Murray, 2006 Jan 25; 5_120; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Paula Moya, 2004 Feb 3; 5_121; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Graduate dissertations, 2002 Dec 4; 5_122; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - David Brady, 2005 Jan 13; 5_123; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - David Brady, 2005 Jan 13; 5_124; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Eavan Boland, 2004 Oct 13; 5_125; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Joel Beinin, 2007 Jan 17; 5_126; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - unlabeled, 2007 Jan 17; 5_127; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Barr, undated; 5_128; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - David Henry Hwang with Hilton Obenzinger, 2007 Feb 13; 5_129; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - David Henry Hwang with Hilton Obenzinger, 2007 Feb 13; 5_130; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - David Henry Huang with Hilton Obenzinger, 2007 Feb 13; 5_131; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - George Fredrickson, 2003 May 8; 5_132; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Arnold Rampersad, 2007 May 21; 5_133; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Professor Ramon Saldivar, 2007 Nov 14; 5_134; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Professor Ramon Saldivar, 2007 Nov 14; 5_135; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Professor Ramon Saldivar, 2007 Nov 14; 5_136; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Professor Ramon Saldivar, 2007 Nov 14; 5_137; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Professor Ramon Saldivar, 2007 Nov 14; 5_138; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Professor Ramon Saldivar, 2007 Nov 14; 5_139; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Professor Ramon Saldivar, 2007 Nov 14; 5_140; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Professor Ramon Saldivar, 2007 Nov 14; 5_141; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Troy Jollimore, 2007 Apr 25; 5_142; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Arnold Rampersad, 2007 May 21; 5_143; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Arnold Rampersad, 2007 May 21; 5_144; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Arnold Rampersad, 2007 May 21; 5_145; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Arnold Rampersad, 2007 May 21; 5_146; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Arnold Rampersad, 2007 May 21; 5_147; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Arnold Rampersad, 2007 May 21; 5_148; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Arnold Rampersad, 2007 May 21; 5_149; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Arnold Rampersad, 2007 May 21; 5_150; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Arnold Rampersad, 2007 May 21; 5_151; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Arnold Rampersad, 2007 May 21; 5_152; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Arnold Rampersad, 2007 May 21; 5_153; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Arnold Rampersad, 2007 May 21; 5_154; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Arnold Rampersad, 2007 May 21; 5_155; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Arnold Rampersad, 2007 May 21; 5_156; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Arnold Rampersad, 2007 May 21; 5_157; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Arnold Rampersad, 2007 May 21; 5_158; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Arnold Rampersad, 2007 May 21; 5_159; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Arnold Rampersad, 2007 May 21; 5_160; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Arnold Rampersad, 2007 May 21; 5_161; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Arnold Rampersad, 2007 May 21; 5_162; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Arnold Rampersad, 2007 May 21; 5_163; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Arnold Rampersad, 2007 May 21; 5_164; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Arnold Rampersad, 2007 May 21; 5_165; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Arnold Rampersad, 2007 May 21; 5_166; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Arnold Rampersad, 2007 May 21; 5_167; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Arnold Rampersad, 2007 May 21; 5_168; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Arnold Rampersad, 2007 May 21; 5_169; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Arnold Rampersad, 2007 May 21; 5_170; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Arnold Rampersad, 2007 May 21; 5_171; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Arnold Rampersad, 2007 May 21; 5_172; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Richard Ford, undated; 5_173; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Richard Ford, undated; 5_174; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Richard Ford, undated; 5_175; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Richard Ford, undated; 5_176; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Richard Ford, undated; 5_177; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Nancy Etchemendy, 2008 Nov 15; 5_178; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Nancy Etchemendy, 2008 Nov 15; 5_179; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Nancy Etchemendy, 2008 Nov 15; 5_180; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Nancy Etchemendy, 2008 Nov 15; 5_181; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Nancy Etchemendy, 2008 Nov 15; 5_182; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Nancy Etchemendy, 2008 Nov 15; 5_183; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Hiton Obenzinger, 2007 Oct 23; 5_184; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - President Hennessy, 2004 Apr 13; 5_185; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Abernethy, 2002 Feb 13; 5_186; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - JoAnne Akalanitis Jim Leverett, 2007 Nov 1; 5_187; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - JoAnne Akalanitis Jim Leverett, 2007 Nov 1; 5_188; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - Estelle Freedman, 2003 Oct 29; 5_189; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - James Hohmann, Julie Klein, Daniel Novinson Emma Trotter, 2008 Jan 23; 5_190; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - tape 1, 2010 May 13; 6_001; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 6)
  - tape 2, 2010 May 13; 6_002; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 6)
  - Gwyneth Lewis, 2010 Mar 8; 6_003; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 6)
  - Gwyneth Lewis, 2010 Mar 8; 6_004; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 6)
  - Rebecca Solnit, 2010 Apr 29; 6_005; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 6)
  - unlabeled, undated; 6_006; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - unlabeled, undated; 6_007; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - Rickford, undated; 6_008; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - unlabeled, undated; 6_009; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - unlabeled, undated; 6_010; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - unlabeled, undated; 6_011; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - Robinson, undated; 6_012; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - Lunsford, undated; 6_013; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - Sianne Ngai, undated; 6_014; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - Roberts, undated; 6_015; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - Bravman, undated; 6_016; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - Student dissertations, undated; 6_017; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)